Skip to main content navigation region started

Account

Articles:

Help:

Main region started

Privacy Policy
==============

**Updated: December, 2023** 

Visible values your business and is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy sets forth our policies and practices for the collection, use and sharing of your information. Visible is a member of the Verizon family of companies.

**I. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION**

We, and service providers acting on our behalf, collect information when you visit our websites, use our apps, contact us, and when you subscribe to and use our wireless service.

**We collect information you provide directly to us.** This includes personal information such as your name, email address, phone number, postal address, a username and password, payment information, and communications you send to us.

**We collect information when you use our service.** This includes information about the calls you make and receive, text messages you send and receive, when you visit our websites or use our app, and wireless network and device information, including location, Internet protocol (IP) address and connection speed, mobile telephone number, device and advertising identifiers, browser type, and operating system. Some Visible devices include Verizon-provided system applications that collect information about network and device conditions, which is used to secure and improve our network and services.

**We also collect information when you visit our sites and use our apps, including through cookies and similar technology.** This includes your IP address, mobile number, device and advertising identifiers; browser and platform type, operating system, connection speed and other attributes; pages that you visit before and after visiting our sites; the date and time of your visit; information about the links you click and pages you view within the sites and screen records.

**We collect info when you contact us, seek technical support, or enter a Visible-sponsored contest, sweepstake or promotion.** When you contact us or we contact you, we and our vendors may monitor or record that communication for quality assurance, to train or support employees, resources or systems, and security purposes.

**We collect information about you from others.** We may obtain information about you from other sources, including from companies that collect consumer information such as demographic and interest data, and lead information we receive from “refer a friend” and similar programs. In addition, if you access social media platforms, such as Facebook, Google, Instagram, Reddit or Twitter, from our sites or apps, to log into our sites or apps, to share information about your experience or to interact with us, we may collect information from these third-party services. We may also collect risk scores and other indicators from companies that help us identify fraud.

**II. USE OF INFORMATION**

We use the information we collect to deliver service, to market to you, and for other business purposes, including to:

* Fulfill your requests for products, services, information and customer support;
    
* Establish and maintain your account;
    
* Determine products and services that may interest you and market them to you, including on Visible sites and apps and on others’ sites, services, apps and devices as described in Section V below;
    
* Analyze the use of the sites, apps, and service for our purposes, such as product and service enhancements;
    
* Research and develop new products and services;
    
* Authenticate you;
    
* Customize the content you see when you use our sites and apps;
    
* Manage and protect our network, services, employees and users;
    
* Detect and prevent potentially prohibited, fraudulent or illegal activities and otherwise in accordance with our [Terms of Use](https://www.verizon.com/about/terms-conditions/terms-of-use); and
    
* For any other purposes disclosed to you at the time we collect your information or with your consent.

**We use some types of information for additional purposes.** We use information from your chats and calls with our service and support representatives to help train employees and support resources and systems to better serve you.

We use information surveys for the purpose for which you provide it, or as described at the time when you submitted the information.

We, our vendors, and third party companies, collect information from our sites and apps for operational purposes such as improving website and app security, authenticating you, detecting and deterring fraud, improving site performance and providing content and analytics. We and these vendors and third-party companies may use [cookies, pixels, tags, web beacons, and scripts, or similar technologies](#beacons) on our pages and the browsers you use and may access advertising identifiers from your mobile device operating systems.

**We may de-identify or aggregate information so that Visible or others may use it for business and marketing purposes.** For example, the data we aggregate might be used to analyze, personalize and improve our service, to provide business and marketing insights to others and to help make advertising more relevant to you. You have choices about some of these uses which are described in the Your Choices section below.

**III. DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION** 

We share information within our company, with vendors and partners who do work on our behalf and for other business purposes described in this policy.

**We share certain information with Verizon, and our affiliates.** This includes providing you with the latest information about our products and services and offer you the latest promotions. 

**We share information with vendors who do work on our behalf.** We use vendors to help us offer, provide, repair, restore and bill for services. We share information with them as necessary for them to perform work for us. They are required to protect the information we share with them or they collect on our behalf and use it only for the specific purposes that we allow. 

**We share information with select partners.** We share your information with select partners that help us with a variety of things, including development and delivery of our sites, apps and service. This includes services provided by others to help us with analytics, including [Google Analytics](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites), which may include storing and accessing cookies and other information on your computer or wireless device.

**We share information about your activity on our websites and apps.** If you access third-party services, such as Facebook, Google, Instagram, Reddit or Twitter, through our sites or apps, to log in or to share information about your Visible experience, or if you contact us through these services, these third-party services may be able to collect information about you and they may notify your connections on the third-party services about your use of the site or app, in accordance with their own privacy policies.

We allow certain third-party advertising companies to collect information about your activity on our sites and in our app, or may send information to them. They can use that information to help us provide more relevant Visible advertisements on our own site and on others’ sites and apps. These ads may be tailored for you based on your activity on Visible sites and combined with your activities on other websites and in apps where these advertising companies are present. These advertising companies may also use information they collect on other sites to determine whether you fit into an audience that advertisers, including Visible, are trying to reach. 

We and these companies may use cookies, pixels, tags, web beacons, scripts, application programming interfaces (APIs) or similar technologies on our pages and the browsers you use and may access advertising or other identifiers from your mobile device operating systems.

Our customers and website visitors can limit the sale and sharing of personal information for certain purposes and can limit the use of this information for certain types of targeted advertising. Some state laws give consumers the right to make these opt out choices. 

In addition, we require that advertising companies disclose when they are using interest-based advertising techniques to deliver ads on our sites and apps as well as when they deliver Visible ads on other sites. We also require them to offer you the ability to opt out of this use of your information.

Visible websites may also include social network or other third-party plug-ins, widgets, or other similar technology that may provide information to associated social networks or third parties even if you do not click on or otherwise interact with the plug-ins and widgets.

Please visit the Your Choices section of this policy to learn how to opt out.

**We may also share information in other situations.**

* **Select partners.** We share your information with partners that help us with a variety of things, including development and delivery of our sites, apps and service. This includes services provided by others to help us with analytics, including [Google Analytics](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites), which may include storing and accessing cookies and other information on your computer or wireless device.
    
* **Business transfers.** We may share your information in connection with a substantial corporate transaction, such as a merger, consolidation, asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.
    
* **Legal purposes.** We may disclose information (1) to respond to legal process, such as subpoenas and court orders, legal claims or government inquiries, and in emergencies such as those involving the danger of death or serious injury to any person; (2) to advance, protect or defend the rights, interests, property, safety, and security of Visible, our affiliates, users, or the public; (3) to identify, protect against, and address unauthorized or unlawful use of our sites, apps or service, or our network; and (4) to outside auditors and regulators.
* **To protect you, others or us.** This includes protecting our rights, property or the safety of our customers or employees; in cases involving danger of death or serious physical injury to any person or other emergencies; to protect against fraudulent malicious, abusive, unauthorized or unlawful use of our products and services and to protect our network, services, devices and users from such use.
* **Aggregated and De-identified Information.** We may aggregate or otherwise de-identify information and use it for our own purposes or share it with third parties for their own purposes.
    
* **With your consent.** We may share information for any other purposes disclosed to you at the time we collect the information or pursuant to your consent.

**IV. INFORMATION SECURITY AND RETENTION** 

We use technical, administrative and physical safeguards to help protect against unauthorized access to, use or disclosure of information we collect or store. In addition, we train our employees on the importance of privacy and security, as well as the proper ways to access, use or disclose customer information. Our practices and policies prohibit employees with whom we share this information from using sensitive information unless they are authorized to do so and have a business need. 

Our policies require that we retain records for as long as they are needed to provide you service or for legal, tax, audit, investigative, and/or security purposes and then securely delete or destroy them.  

We incorporate personal information into different types of records, not always by distinct data elements. For example, your name is part of your account, billing, technical support and call detail records.

Although we strive to keep information secure, we can’t guarantee that our safeguards will prevent every unauthorized [attempt to access](https://www.verizon.com/about/privacy/full-privacy-policy#), use or disclose personal information. We use our security and incident response plans to handle such incidents.

**V. YOUR CHOICES**

You have choices about certain ways we use and share information about you. 

**Marketing.** You have choices about receiving marketing from Visible. If you would like to be removed from Visible’s email marketing list, you can opt out using the unsubscribe instructions, usually found at the bottom of the emails.

**Website information used for interest based advertising.** You can limit the sale and sharing of personal information for certain purposes as well as limit the use of this information for certain types of targeted advertising. Some state laws give consumers the right to make these opt out choices. 

You can opt out by visiting [Your Privacy Choices](https://www.visible.com/legal/privacy-choices) . This page also describes how we honor [Global Privacy Control signals](https://globalprivacycontrol.org/) you may set in your browser. We do not currently respond to [Do Not Track signals](https://allaboutdnt.com/) in your web browser setting. If you opt out, you may still see Visible advertisements, but they may not be as relevant to you.

You can also visit the industry-wide [Digital Advertising Alliance opt-out page](https://www.aboutads.info/) or click on this icon  available in or around online advertisements placed using interest-based advertising techniques to learn more and opt out of the use of your information for this type of advertising. Click on this icon provides additional information on the companies and data practices that were used to deliver the ad and describes how you may opt out of these advertising programs. Similarly, you have choices about allowing this type of advertising on your mobile device. On Apple devices, you will only be included in this activity if you opt-in. You can review or change an app’s tracking permission by going to your device Setting>Privacy>Tracking. On Android devices, you can opt out using your device setting to “Opt out of Ads Personalization.”

**VI. INTERNATIONAL USERS** 

Our sites, apps and service are designed for and targeted to U.S. audiences and are governed by and operated in accordance with the laws of the U.S. We make no representation that our apps, sites or services are operated in accordance with the laws or regulations of any other nation. By using our apps, sites or service and providing us with information, you understand and agree that your information may be transferred to and stored on servers located outside your resident jurisdiction and, to the extent you are a resident of a country other than the United States, that you consent to the transfer of such data to the United States for processing by us in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### VII. STATE PRIVACY RIGHTS

**CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

**California Consumer Privacy Act** 

The California Consumer Privacy Act, or CCPA, provides California residents with specific rights.

The law provides you with the right to know what information we collect about you and how we use it; to access and delete that information within certain limits; to request that we correct information that you believe is inaccurate; to tell us not to sell or share personal information about you; to limit the use of certain sensitive personal information; and to not be discriminated against for invoking these rights.

**Your Right to Know** 

You have the right to know what personal information we collect, how we use it, and how long we keep it. This policy provides details about our collection and use practices. We collect personal information when you interact with us and use our products and services, such as when you place an order, have questions about your service, communicate with us by chat or phone, seek technical support, contact us on social media, visit our website, or enter a Visible-sponsored or affiliated contest, sweepstake or promotion. We also collect information from certain third-party sources and from our network and the devices you use. 

Depending on what products and services you use and how you interact with us, we may collect these categories of personal information:

* Identifiers, including, name, billing and email address, mobile device identifiers, IP address, account credentials, and other similar identifiers
    
* Legally protected classifications, including race, ancestry, gender, and disability if you provide them to us
    
* Commercial information, including products or services you purchase and consider
    
* Internet information, including browsing history, search and other activity on our site, and information regarding your interaction with our websites applications, and advertisements
    
* Geolocation data from our apps when you permit it
    
* Audio, electronic, visual, or similar information, such as voice recordings of customer service calls 
    
* Inferences drawn from any of the information described above to create a profile reflecting your preferences, characteristics, predispositions, and behavior.  
    
* Secure Account Information including account log-in, financial account, debit card, or credit card number in combination with any required security or access code, password, or credentials allowing access to an account 
    
* And other information that may identify, relate to, describe, or is capable of being associated with you.

Some of the information we collect may be considered sensitive personal information under this California law which defines sensitive information to include account log-in information with required security or access codes; financial account, debit or credit card number along with required security or access code, password, or credentials allowing access to an account; precise geolocation when you allow it in our app; and the contents of your mail, email, and text messages unless we are the recipient of the communication.

We use this information for business and commercial purposes as they are defined by the CCPA. Business and commercial purposes include providing you products and services, operating our business and engaging in economic activities such as communicating with you and providing customer service; personalizing your experiences; improving our services; providing marketing and advertising; debugging; auditing our processes and services; short-term transient uses; research; and security, fraud, and legal compliance purposes. 

We share information with service providers as necessary for them to perform work for us. We share with them the information they need to perform that work. This includes personal information about you. For example, we share contact information with service providers who help us send Visible marketing campaigns. Service providers are required to protect the information we share with them or they collect on our behalf and use it only for the specific purposes that we allow. 

We may also disclose information with your consent and as further described in other sections of this policy.

Our policies require that we retain records for as long they are needed for legal, tax, audit, investigative, and/or security purposes and then securely delete or destroy them. We incorporate personal information into different types of records; it is not always retained by distinct data elements. For example, your name could be part of your customer account record, transaction record, or call records. Each type of record may be retained for a different time period depending on its purpose. We have established criteria for how long to keep different types of records.

**Your Right to Access or Correct Information**

You have the right to request access to specific pieces and categories of personal information we collect by using our [Data and Privacy Portal](https://www.visible.com/legal/data-and-privacy-portal) or via the email address provided below.  We will provide this information to you in a portable and readily usable format. We will honor up to two consumer rights requests every twelve months as required by California law. You can use this same contact information to request that we correct inaccurate personal information we have about you.

**Your Right to Delete** 

You have the right to request that Visible delete personal information we have about you unless we need it for specific reasons. These reasons include: needing the information to provide the services you have requested and other activities needed to maintain ongoing business relationship with you, to maintain information security, to exercise legal rights and to comply with other laws. All the personal information we retain today is only used for these purposes. We retain the information that we collect only as long as needed for these purposes.

**Your Right to Opt Out of the Sale or Sharing of Personal Information** 

California law defines “sale or sharing” broadly to include sharing personal information for monetary or other valuable consideration and the sharing of personal information for cross contextual advertising purposes. The definition does not cover all sharing of personal information. We do not knowingly sell or share personal information related to children under 16 years of age.  

Since 2022 and presently, our activities that fall under the definition of “sale or sharing” under California law are: 

* using third-party advertising companies that collect information about your visit to our websites and app using cookies and other web technologies to inform our and others’ cross contextual advertising;
    
* sharing customer information with third-party advertising and social media companies to help them better target our advertising on their websites and applications;
    
* sharing customer information with third-parties to help find other potential customers using interest segments they create from your activities across non-affiliated websites and apps.

You can opt out of sale or sharing by accessing our [Your Privacy Choices](https://www.visible.com/legal/privacy-choices)  site. This page also describes how we honor [Global Privacy Control](https://globalprivacycontrol.org/) (GPC) signals you may set on your browser. We do not respond to Do Not Track signals.    

If you are a Visible member who is logged in to your account when using the GPC signal, we will apply your choice to activity on our website whenever you are logged in and to non-website activities across your account.  However, if you are not logged in or don’t have an account and use a GPC, we will opt you out of sharing activity on our sites, but may need more information from you to identify you and apply your choice to non-website sharing activities.

**Your Right to Limit the Use of Sensitive Personal Information**

You have the right to ask us to limit the use and disclosure of sensitive personal information if we use that information for purposes beyond what is needed to provide the products and services you request or for other reasons specified in the law. We do not use or disclose sensitive personal information for other purposes without your consent so we do not offer you an option to limit the use of sensitive personal information. The purposes for which we might use sensitive personal information include: detecting security incidents; resisting malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal actions; ensuring the physical safety of a person; short-term, transient uses; performing services such as maintaining or servicing accounts, providing customer service, fulfilling orders and transactions; verifying your information; and verifying, maintaining or enhancing a service on a device that is owned manufactured or controlled by us or on your device. We may also share your information with service providers providing storage or similar services on our behalf.

**Your Right to Not Be Discriminated Against** 

We do not discriminate against you if you exercise any rights described in this section. We will not deny goods or services, charge different prices or rates for goods or services, or provide you a different level or quality of goods and services. You also have the right to receive information about the financial incentives that we offer to you.

**Where to Exercise Your Rights**

You or your authorized agent can exercise your right to access or correct data by:

* Visiting the Visible [Data and Privacy Portal](https://www.visible.com/legal/data-and-privacy-portal)
    
* Sending an email to [privacy@visible.com](mailto:privacy@visible.com) 

You can exercise your right to opt-out of sale or sharing of personal information by visiting our [Your Privacy Choices](https://www.visible.com/legal/privacy-choices)  page.

If you visit or use one of our other sites you must separately opt out using these sites’ “Your Privacy Choices ” webpages at [Visible Community Your Privacy Choices](http://community.visible.com/t5/custom/page/page-id/yourprivacychoices) or in the footer of the [Visible Merch website](https://www.visiblemerch.com/).

If you visit [Visible Offers](https://www.visibleoffers.com//#/home), you will have to separately opt out. Our selling and sharing activity for [Visible Offers](https://www.visibleoffers.com//#/home) is limited to activity on the [Visible Offers](https://www.visibleoffers.com//#/home) website. We use third-party advertising companies that collect information about your visit to the [Visible Offers](https://www.visibleoffers.com//#/home) site using cookies and other web technologies to better tailor advertising to you for us and others. You can opt out of selling and sharing of your activity by turning off “Functional and Performance” and “Advertising” cookies in the cookie settings that can be accessed from the [Your Privacy Choices](https://www.visible.com/legal/privacy-choices)  link in the footer of the [Visible Offers](https://www.visibleoffers.com//#/home) site, or by managing your settings through the cookie banner that displays on your first visit to the site. If you opt out of Functional and Performance and Advertising cookies, only web tech that is required for the site to function will operate during your visit. Your opt out will apply on the browser and device you used when you opted out.  If you visit the site from a different device or browser, or clear your cookies from your browser history, you will need to opt out again. The [Visible Offers](https://www.visibleoffers.com//#/home) site also honors browser-based [Global Privacy Control](https://globalprivacycontrol.org/) (GPC) signals that you may set in your browser as an opt out when you visit the Offers site.

You can authorize an agent to exercise your California privacy rights on your behalf. To designate a business or individual as your agent, use our Data and Privacy Portal to “Assign and manage your authorized agent.” We may require additional proof that you granted the authority.

We require you to verify your identity using the processes we describe in the portal or the privacy choices page before we fulfill your request. Depending on the type of request you make, you may be required to log into an existing account and prove access to your mobile phone or to the email address on file with us.

We will endeavor to respond to your requests within 45 days, but it may take up to 90 days. If we need more than 45 days, we will contact you to let you know that we need additional time.

Are you a Visible Merch Store customer? Please visit the [Visible Merch Store Privacy Policy](https://www.visiblemerch.com/visible/privacy-policy) for information about how to exercise your rights.

Are you a Visible Communities user?  Please visit the [Visible Community Privacy Policy](https://community.visible.com/t5/Get-Started/Privacy-Policy/ba-p/2) for information about how to exercise your rights

**Reporting**

The table below reports the number of verified requests to know received from consumers and other individuals in 2022. Because all personal information collected from users is required to provide service, consumers and other individuals do not have the option to delete personal information. Visible also received 79 unverified requests to know and 101 unverified requests to delete via email in 2022.

|     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
|     | **Request to Delete** | **Requests to Know** |
| **Total Requests** | N/A | 6008 |
| **Complied With** | N/A | 5997 |
| **Denied** | N/A | 11  |
| **Average Response Time (Days)** | N/A | 5   |

As described above, Visible allows third-party advertising companies to collect information about activity from website visitors and in our apps, for example through cookies and similar technologies, mobile ad identifiers, pixels, web beacons and social network plugins. These ad entities use information they collect to help us provide more relevant Visible advertisements and for other advertising purposes.  During 2022, consumers could learn about this activity and how to opt out on Visible’s “Do Not Sell My Personal Information” webpage. This webpage became Visible’s [Your Privacy Choices](https://www.visible.com/legal/privacy-choices)  webpage in December 2022.  Between January 1, 2022 and December 31, 2022, there were approximately 65,518 unique visitors to the “Do Not Sell My Personal Information” or “Your Privacy Choices” webpage, however, because the opt out tools available during that time are managed directly by consumers on their devices, we do not have metrics for the number of consumers who opted out.

If you have questions about your rights under California law, email us at [privacy@visible.com](mailto:privacy@visible.com) .  

**Other California Privacy Rights**

California customers may request, once per year, that we disclose the identity of any third parties with whom we have shared personal information for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes within the previous calendar year, along with the type of personal information disclosed. If you have any questions about your rights under this law, email us at [privacy@visible.com](mailto:privacy@visible.com) .

California residents under age 18 who are registered users of online sites, services or applications may request and obtain removal of content or information they have publicly posted. Your request should include a detailed description of the specific content or information to be removed. Please be aware that your request does not guarantee complete or comprehensive removal of content or information posted online and that the law may not permit or require removal in certain circumstances.

**COLORADO PRIVACY RIGHTS**  

The Colorado Privacy Act gives specific rights to Colorado residents. This law gives you the right to know whether we collect information about you, what that information is and how we use it; access information we have about you in a commonly used format; delete certain information; request that we correct information that you believe is inaccurate; and opt out of having personal information about you sold, used for targeted advertising to you, or used to build a profile about you to make legal or similar significant decisions about you. 

**You have the right to know whether we collect personal information, what it is and the purposes for which we use it.**  

This privacy policy describes the personal information we collect and how we use it. We collect personal information when you interact with us and use our products and services, from certain third-party sources and from the devices you use. Colorado law requires us to let you know the categories of personal information we collect and the purposes for which we collect it and with whom we may share them. This includes:

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Contact and device information (including name, billing and email address, mobile device identifiers, IP address, account credentials, business customer representative contact information, other similar identifiers)<br><br>Commercial information such as products and services you purchase or consider and financial information<br><br>Internet or electronic network activity (including browsing history, search history on our site, and information regarding our interactions with our websites, applications and advertisements). | We use this information to provide our products and services, operate our businesses, communicate with you and provide customer service; personalize your experiences; improve our services; provide marketing and advertising; create business insights;  debug problems, audit our processes and services; short-term transient uses; research; and security, fraud, and legal compliance. |
| Geolocation data from our apps when you permit it.<br><br>Information about how you use our products and services. | We use this information for the purpose for which you allow us when you provide consent, for business operations, security and fraud prevention; to personalize your experiences and our marketing. |
| Demographic and interest information you provide or we obtain from third parties.<br><br>Inferences drawn from information reflecting your preferences, characteristics, predispositions and behaviors. | We use this information to help us better understand our customers and our markets, better personalize your experiences, provide marketing and advertising, test for bias and create business insights. |
| Secure Account Information including account log-in, financial account, debit card, or credit card number in combination with any required security or access code, password, or credentials allowing access to an account. | We use this to provide you with access to your account, accept payment for products and services you purchase, security and fraud prevention and legal compliance purposes. |
| Audio, electronic, visual or similar information, such as voice recordings of customer service calls and photographs of customer equipment. | We use this information to troubleshoot service, to improve our service and for quality assurance, help us better understand our customers and our markets, personalize your experiences, security and fraud prevention, provide marketing and advertising, test for bias and create business insights. |
| Other information that may identify, relate to, describe, or is capable of being associated with you. | For example, we may collect your insurance policy number to process damage claims. |

Some of the information that we collect may be sensitive data under Colorado law which is also referred to as sensitive personal information in this policy. The law defines sensitive data as personal data revealing racial or ethnic origin, religious beliefs, mental or physical health condition or diagnosis, sex life or sexual orientation, or citizenship or citizenship status; processing genetic or biometric data for the purpose of uniquely identifying you; and personal data collected from a known child.    

**You have the right to access and correct information.**

You can access specific pieces and categories of personal information we collected by using our [Data and Privacy Portal](https://www.visible.com/legal/data-and-privacy-portal) or via the email address provided below. To the extent technically feasible, we will provide this information to you in a portable and readily usable format. You can use this same contact information to request that we correct inaccurate personal information we have about you.  

**You have the right to delete information.**

You have the right to request that Visible delete personal information we have unless we need it for reasons specified in the Colorado law. These reasons include: complying with laws and cooperating with law enforcement in good faith; investigating, establishing, preparing or defending against legal claims; internal research to improve, repair, or develop products; identifying and repairing errors; internal operations; providing products and services you use; protecting vital interests and certain public interests; preventing fraud; and assisting another with compliance. All the personal information that we retain today is only used for these purposes. We retain the information we collect only as long as needed for these purposes.  

**You have the right to tell us not to sell personal information or use it for targeted advertising purposes.**  

Colorado law defines “sale” to mean the exchange of personal data for monetary or other valuable consideration. The law describes “targeted advertising” as using personal information obtained or inferred over time from your activities across non-affiliated websites, applications or online services to predict your preferences or interests and target advertising to you.   

Our activities that fall under the definition of “sale” or “targeted advertising” under Colorado law are: 

* using third-party advertising companies’ cookies, pixels, tags, and other web technologies on our site to collect  information about your activity on our site during your visit  which can be used and combined with other information about you from your activity and behavior across unaffiliated websites and apps to tailor the ads you see from us and others;
    
* sharing consumer information with third-party advertising and social media companies to help them better target our advertising on their websites and applications and to help find other potential customers using interest segments and audiences they create from your activities across non-affiliated websites and apps; and
    
* using consumer information we obtain from third-parties to better customize our advertising, when that information is derived from your activities across non-affiliated sites and apps.

You can opt out of the sale of personal information and targeted advertising by visiting [Your Privacy Choices](https://www.visible.com/legal/privacy-choices)  page. 

**You have the right to tell us not to use personal information to establish profiles to make decisions that produce legal or similarly significant effects.**

We do not use personal information to profile you to further decisions that have legal or similar significant effects.  

**Use of Sensitive Personal Information.**

Colorado law prohibits us from using sensitive personal information without your consent, except for purposes specified in the law. These purposes include: complying with laws, rules, regulations, investigative subpoena or summons by governmental authorities; cooperating with law enforcement; investigating, establishing, preparing or defending against legal claims; providing and maintaining the products and services you use, preventing and responding to security and other significant incidents; and taking immediate steps to protect an interest that is essential for the life or physical safety of you or another natural person; and using information for short-term transient purposes such as displaying relevant information to you based on your activity during a single transaction. We only use sensitive personal information as you authorize with your express consent or as authorized under the law.    

**You can appeal a denial of your request to exercise any of the privacy rights provided by the Colorado law.**

If we deny your request, we will notify you and you may submit an appeal using a link we provide. You may also submit an appeal by emailing us at [privacy@visible.com](mailto:privacy@visible.com) . Please use the subject line "APPEAL" and provide your name, contact information including phone number, a description of the decision you are appealing, and the reason for your appeal. If we deny your appeal, you may contact the Colorado Attorney General with any concerns.  

**We do not discriminate against you.**

We do not discriminate against you if you exercise any rights described in this section, by denying you goods or services, charging different prices or rates for goods or services or providing you a different level or quality of goods and services.  

**Where to exercise your rights.**

You can exercise your right to access, delete, or correct data by:

* Visiting the Visible [Data and Privacy Portal](https://www.visible.com/legal/data-and-privacy-portal)
    
* Sending an email to  [privacy@visible.com](mailto:privacy@visible.com) 

You can exercise your right to opt-out of sale of personal information or use of it for targeted advertising by visiting our [Your Privacy Choices](https://www.visible.com/legal/privacy-choices) page. This page also provides a link for your authorized agent to opt out on your behalf.

If you visit or use one of our other sites you must separately opt out using these sites’ “Your Privacy Choices” webpages at [Visible Community Your Privacy Choices](http://community.visible.com/t5/custom/page/page-id/yourprivacychoices) or in the footer of the [Visible Merch website](https://www.visiblemerch.com/).

If you visit Visible Offers, you will have to separately opt out. Our selling and sharing activity for Visible Offers is limited to activity on the Visible Offers website. We use third-party advertising companies that collect information about your visit to the Visible Offers site using cookies and other web technologies to better tailor advertising to you for us and others.  You can opt out of the sale and use and sharing of your activity for behavioral targeted advertising by turning off “Functional and Performance” and “Advertising” cookies in the cookie settings that can be accessed from the Your Privacy Choices link in the footer of the Visible Offers site, or by managing your settings through the cookie banner that displays on your first visit to the site.  If you opt out of Functional and Performance and Advertising cookies, only web tech that is required for the site to function will operate during your visit. Your opt out will apply on the browser and device you used when you opted out. If you visit the site from a different device or browser, or clear your cookies from your browser history, you will need to opt out again. The Visible Offers site also honor browser-based [Global Privacy Control](https://globalprivacycontrol.org/) (GPC) signals that you may set in your browser, as an opt out when you visit the Offers site. 

We require you to verify your identity using the processes described in the portal before we fulfill your request.

We will endeavor to respond to your requests within 45 days, but it may take up to 90 days. If we need more than 45 days, we will contact you to let you know that we need additional time.

Are you a Visible Merch Store customer? Please visit the [Visible Merch Store Privacy Policy](https://www.visiblemerch.com/visible/privacy-policy) for information about how to exercise your rights.

Are you a Visible Communities user?  Please visit the [Visible Community Privacy Policy](https://community.visible.com/t5/Get-Started/Privacy-Policy/ba-p/2) for information about how to exercise your rights.

If you have questions about your rights under Colorado law, email us at [privacy@visible.com](mailto:%20privacy@visible.com) 

**CONNECTICUT PRIVACY RIGHTS**  

The Connecticut Data Privacy Act gives specific rights to Connecticut residents. This law gives you the right to know whether we collect information about you;  access, correct and delete certain information; opt out of having personal information about you sold or used for certain targeted advertising purposes, or to prevent us from using artificial intelligence to create a profile about you to make legal or similar significant decisions about you. 

**You have the right to know whether we collect personal information about you.**

This privacy policy provides details about our information collection and use practices. Connecticut law requires us to let you know the categories of personal information we collect and use. Depending on what products and services you use and how you interact with us, we may collect these categories of personal information:

* Contact and device information (including, name, billing and email address, mobile device identifiers, IP address, and account credentials); information about the products and services you purchase; information about your browsing, search and other activity on our sites and app as well as your interactions with our sites, app, and advertisements.
    
* Demographic and interest information that you provide or that we obtain from third parties.
    
* Geolocation information from our apps when you permit it; information about how you use our products and services; voice recordings of customer service calls and chat and call transcripts when you engage with us.
    
* Secure Account Information including account log-in, financial account, debit card, or credit card number in combination with any required security or access code, password, or credentials allowing access to an account 
    
* And other information that may identify, relate to, describe, or is capable of being associated with you.is capable of being associated with you. 

We use this information for business purposes including: providing you products and services; operating our business; communicating with you and providing customer service; personalizing your experiences; improving our services; providing marketing and advertising; debugging; auditing our processes and services; short-term transient uses; research; and security, fraud, and legal compliance.   

We share information with service providers (also known as processors) as necessary for them to perform work for us. They are required to protect the information they receive or they collect on our behalf and use it only for the specific purposes that we allow. We may also disclose information with your consent and as detailed elsewhere in this policy.

**You have the right to access and correct information.**

You can access certain personal information we collected using our [Data and Privacy Portal](https://www.visible.com/legal/data-and-privacy-portal) or via the email address provided below. To the extent technically feasible, we will provide this information to you in a portable and readily usable format. You can use this same contact information to request that we correct inaccurate personal information we have about you. 

**You have the right to delete information.**

You have the right to request that Visible delete personal information we have about you unless we need it for specific reasons. These reasons include: comply with laws, rules, regulations, investigative subpoena or summons by governmental authorities; defending against legal claims; providing and maintaining the products and services you use, performing a contract, preventing and responding to security and other significant incidents; and taking immediate steps to protect an interest that is essential for the life or physical safety of you or another natural person, and short-term transient purposes such as displaying relevant information to you based on your activity during a single interaction and then securely deleting it. All the personal information we retain today is only used for these purposes. We retain this information only as long as necessary for these purposes and then securely delete it.

**Your right to opt out of the sale of personal information and the use of personal information for targeted advertising.**

Connecticut law defines “sale” to mean the exchange of personal data for monetary or other valuable consideration. Connecticut law defines “targeted advertising” as using personal data obtained or inferred from your activities over time and across nonaffiliated Internet web sites or online applications  to predict your preferences or interests, and display advertising to you. 

Our activities that fall under the definition of “sale” or “targeted advertising” under Connecticut law are: 

* using third-party advertising companies’ cookies, pixels, tags, and other web technologies on our site to collect  information about your activity on our site during your visit  which can be used and combined with other information about you from your activity and behavior across unaffiliated websites and apps to tailor the ads you see from us and others;
    
* sharing consumer information with third-party advertising and social media companies to help them better target our advertising on their websites and applications and to help find other potential customers using interest segments and audiences they create from your activities across 
    
* non-affiliated websites and apps; and
    
* using consumer information we obtain from third-parties to better customize our advertising, when that information is derived from your activities across non-affiliated sites and apps.

You can exercise your right to opt out by visiting our [Your Privacy Choices](https://www.visible.com/legal/privacy-choices)  page.

**You have the right to tell us not to use personal information to establish profiles to make decisions that produce legal or similarly significant effects.**

We do not use personal information to profile you to further decisions that have legal or similar significant effects. 

**Use of sensitive personal information**

Connecticut law prohibits us from using sensitive personal information without your consent except as specified in the law. Sensitive personal information includes: data revealing racial or ethnic origin, religious beliefs, mental or physical health condition or diagnosis, sex life, sexual orientation or citizenship or immigration status; processing genetic or biometric data for the purpose of uniquely identifying you; personal data collected from a known child; or precise geolocation data.

We use sensitive personal information for purposes authorized by the law or after we obtain your express consent. These purposes include: to comply with laws, rules, regulations, investigative subpoena or summons by government authorities; defend against legal claims; provide and maintain the products and services you use, perform a contract; prevent and respond to security and other significant incidents; and to take immediate steps to protect an interest that is essential for the life or physical safety of you or another natural person; and for short-term transient purposes such as displaying relevant information to you based on your activity during a single interaction.

**You can appeal a denial of your request to exercise any of the privacy rights provided by Connecticut law.**

If we deny your request, we will notify you and you may submit an appeal using a link we provide in the notice.  You may also submit an appeal by emailing us at [privacy@visible.com](mailto:privacy@visible.com) . Please use the subject line "APPEAL" and provide your name, contact information including phone number, a description of the decision you are appealing, and the reason for your appeal. You may also contact the Connecticut Attorney General.

**We do not discriminate against you**

We do not discriminate against you if you exercise any rights described in this section, by denying you goods or services, charging different prices or rates for goods or services or providing you a different level or quality of goods and services.

**Where to exercise your rights.**

You can exercise your right to access, delete, or correct data by:

* Visiting the Visible [Data and Privacy Portal](https://www.visible.com/legal/data-and-privacy-portal)
    
* Sending an email to [privacy@visible.com](mailto:privacy@visible.com) 

You can exercise your right to opt-out of sale of personal information or use of it for targeted advertising by visiting our [Your Privacy Choices](https://www.visible.com/legal/privacy-choices)  page. The page also provides instructions for your authorized agent to opt out on your behalf.  

If you visit or use one of our other sites you must separately opt out using these sites’ “Your Privacy Choices” webpages at [Visible Community Your Privacy Choices](http://community.visible.com/t5/custom/page/page-id/yourprivacychoices) or in the footer on the [Visible Merch website](https://www.visiblemerch.com/). 

If you visit [Visible Offers](https://www.visibleoffers.com//#/home), you will have to separately opt out. We use third-party advertising companies that collect information about your visit to the [Visible Offers](https://www.visibleoffers.com//#/home) site using cookies and other web technologies to better tailor advertising to you for us and others. You can opt out of the sale and use and sharing of your activity for behavioral targeted advertising by turning off “Functional and Performance” and “Advertising” cookies in the cookie settings that can be accessed from the Your Privacy Choices link in the footer of the [Visible Offers](https://www.visibleoffers.com//#/home) site, or by managing your settings through the cookie banner that displays on your first visit to the site. If you opt out of Functional and Performance and Advertising cookies, only web tech that is required for the site to function will operate during your visit.  Your opt out will apply on the browser and device you used when you opted out. If you visit the site from a different device or browser, or clear your cookies from your browser history, you will need to opt out again. The [Visible Offers](https://www.visibleoffers.com//#/home) site also honor browser-based [Global Privacy Control](https://globalprivacycontrol.org/) (GPC) signals that you may set in your browser, as an opt out when you visit the Offers site. 

We require you to verify your identity using the processes described in the portal before we fulfill your request.

We will endeavor to respond to your requests within 45 days, but it may take up to 90 days. If we need more than 45 days, we will contact you to let you know that we need additional time.

Are you a Visible Merch Store customer? Please visit the [Visible Merch Store Privacy Policy](https://www.visiblemerch.com/visible/privacy-policy) for information about how to exercise your rights.

Are you a Visible Communities user?  Please visit the [Visible Community Privacy Policy](https://community.visible.com/t5/Get-Started/Privacy-Policy/ba-p/2) for information about how to exercise your rights.

**MAINE BROADBAND CUSTOMER PRIVACY RIGHTS**

The Maine Broadband Internet Access Service Customer Privacy Act gives  privacy rights to current and former subscribers of mass market broadband Internet access service in Maine, as well as applicants. The Maine law gives you the right to control certain ways that we use or share information we have about you and requires that we provide you with a notice of your rights and our obligations under this law. We do this in this section.

The Maine law also requires us to take reasonable measures to protect customer personal information. We describe this in an earlier section of this privacy policy.

We will not use, disclose, sell, or permit access to broadband customer personal information (personally identifying information about a customer or information from a customer’s use of broadband Internet access service) except with affirmative consent or for the following purposes allowed under the Maine law: to provide and maintain your broadband services; market and advertise our communications-related services to you; comply with lawful court orders; bill and collect; protect users from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful use of or subscription to such services; or provide location information in response to certain emergency situations..

The Maine law also provides you with a right to opt out of any use or sharing of data that is not customer personal information under the law. At this time, we do not collect information about you as a broadband customer that is not customer personal information. If we begin collecting such information in the future, we will give you the right to opt out of its use and sharing.

We will not refuse to provide you with broadband service, charge you a penalty, or offer you a discount based on whether you agree that we can use or share your broadband customer personal information.

**NEVADA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

Nevada law allows consumers to opt out of the sale of personal information by online service providers such as website operators and data brokers. Nevada law defines “sale” as the exchange of certain personally identifiable information for money. Personally identifiable information includes name, address, phone number, Social Security number, or any identifier that can be used to contact a consumer electronically.

Visible does not currently sell personal information as defined by Nevada law and has no plans to start. If Visible ever starts selling such personal information, current Visible customers will be opted out. If you have any questions, please contact us at [privacy@visible.com](mailto:privacy@visible.com) . 

**UTAH PRIVACY NOTICE**

The Utah Consumer Privacy Act gives specific rights to Utah residents. This law may give you the right to know whether we collect information about you; access and delete certain information we collect; obtain a copy of personal information you’ve provided to us; and opt out of having personal information about you sold or used for targeted advertising to you.

**Personal information we collect and how we use it.**

This privacy policy details our collection and use practices. We collect personal information when you interact with us and use our products as services, such as when you place an order or have questions about your account or service; contact us on social media, seek technical support; enter a Visible-sponsored or affiliated contest, sweepstakes, or promotion; or register to receive news or updates. We also collect information from certain third-party sources and from the devices you use.  Depending on what products and services you use and how you interact with us, we may collect these categories of personal information:  

* Contact and device information (including, name, billing and email address, mobile device identifiers, IP address and account credentials); information about the products and services you purchase; information about your browsing, search and other activity on our sites and app as well as your interactions with our sites, app and advertisements.
    
* Demographic and interest information that you provide or that we obtain from third parties.
    
* Geolocation information from our app when you permit it; information about how you use our products and services; and chat transcripts when you engage with us.
    
* Secure Account Information including account log-in, financial account, debit card, or credit card number in combination with any required security or access code, password, or credentials allowing access to an account 
    
* And other information that may identify, relate to, describe, or is capable of being associated with you. 

We use the information we collect for business and commercial purposes which include: providing you products and services, operating our businesses, and engaging in economic activities such as communicating with you and providing customer service; personalizing your experiences; improving our services; providing marketing and advertising; debugging; auditing our processes and services; short-term transient uses; research; and security, fraud, and legal compliance.

We also allow select third parties to directly collect information about your activity on our websites using cookies and  other web technologies. These third parties use information they collect to help us provide more relevant Visible advertisements on other websites and apps and may also use information for their own or others’ advertising purposes.  

**Accessing personal information.**

You can access specific pieces and categories of personal information we collect by accessing our [Data and Privacy Portal](https://www.visible.com/legal/data-and-privacy-portal) or via the email address provided below. To the extent technically feasible, we will provide this information to you in a portable and readily usable format.  

**Requesting that we delete information.**

Utah law may give you the right to request that Visible delete personal information we have about you unless we need it for specific reasons. These reasons include complying with laws, rules, regulations,  or regulatory inquiries, investigations, subpoena or summons by governmental authorities; cooperating with law enforcement agencies; defend against legal claims; providing and maintaining a product or service to you; performing a contract with you; taking immediate steps to protect an interest that is essential for the life of physical safety of you or another individual; detect, prevent and protect against security incident, fraud, harassment, identity theft, malicious or deceptive activity or illegal activity; preserve the integrity or security of our systems or defend against those harming or threatening the integrity or security of our systems; conduct internal analytics or research to develop, improve or repair our products, services or technology; identify and repair technical issues; perform internal operations that are aligned with what you would expect based on our relationship with us or otherwise compatible with processing needed to provide you products or services you request or to perform our agreement or contract with you. We retain information only as long as necessary for these purposes and then securely delete it.  

**Tell us not to sell personal information.**

Utah law defines “sale” to mean the exchange of personal data for monetary consideration. We do not sell information as it is defined under Utah law.  

**Opt-out of targeted advertising.**

Utah law describes “targeted advertising” as using personal data obtained from your activities over time and across nonaffiliated websites or apps to predict your preferences or interests and target advertising to you.  

Our activities that fall under the definition of “targeted advertising” under the Utah law are:

* using third-party advertising companies’ cookies, pixels, tags, and other web technologies on our site to collect  information about your activity on our site during your visit  which can be used and combined with other information about you from your activity and behavior across unaffiliated websites and apps to tailor the ads you see from us and others;
    
* sharing consumer information with third-party advertising and social media companies to help them better target our advertising on their websites and applications and to help find other potential customers using interest segments and audiences they create from your activities across non-affiliated websites and apps; and
    
* using consumer information we obtain from third-parties to better customize our advertising, when that information is derived from your activities across non-affiliated sites and apps.

You can opt out of targeted advertising by accessing [Your Privacy Choices](https://www.visible.com/legal/privacy-choices) .  

**Use of sensitive information**

Utah law may give you the right to opt out of having sensitive personal information used or shared for purposes beyond what is needed to provide the products and services you request for for other reasons specified in the law. Utah law defines sensitive personal information as personal data revealing racial or ethnic origin, religious beliefs, sexual orientation, citizenship or immigration status; medical history, mental or physical health condition, or medical treatment or diagnosis by a health care professional; processing genetic or biometric data for the purpose of uniquely identifying you; and precise geolocation data. The law allows the use of sensitive information for these purposes: complying with laws, rules, regulations,  or regulatory inquiries, investigations, subpoena or summons by governmental authorities; cooperating with law enforcement agencies; defend against legal claims; providing and maintaining a product or service to you; performing a contract with you; taking immediate steps to protect an interest that is essential for the life of physical safety of you or another individual; detect, prevent and protect against security incident, fraud, harassment, identity theft, malicious or deceptive activity or illegal activity; preserve the integrity or security of our systems or defend against those harming or threatening the integrity or security of our systems; conduct internal analytics or research to develop, improve or repair our products, services or technology; identify and repair technical issues; perform internal operations that are aligned with what you would expect based on our relationship with us or otherwise compatible with processing needed to provide you products or services you request or to perform our agreement or contract with you.  

We do not use or disclose sensitive personal information for other purposes without your consent. 

**We do not discriminate against you.**

We do not discriminate against you if you take any of the actions described in this section, by denying you goods or services, charging different prices or rates for goods or services or providing you a different level or quality of goods and services.  

**Where to access personal information, request that we delete information, and opt out of targeted advertising.**

You can access or delete personal information we have about you by:  

* Visiting the Visible [Data and Privacy Portal](https://www.visible.com/legal/data-and-privacy-portal)
    
* Sending an email to  [privacy@visible.com](mailto:privacy@visible.com) 

You can opt-out of targeted advertising by visiting our [Your Privacy Choices](https://www.visible.com/legal/privacy-choices)  page. 

If you visit or use one of our other sites you must separately opt out using these sites’ “Your Privacy Choices” webpages at [Visible Community Your Privacy Choices](http://community.visible.com/t5/custom/page/page-id/yourprivacychoices) or in the footer on the [Visible Merch website](https://www.visiblemerch.com/).

If you visit Visible Offers, you will have to separately opt out. We use third-party advertising companies that collect information about your visit to the Visible Offers site using cookies and other web technologies to better tailor advertising to you for us and others. You can opt out of the sale and use and sharing of your activity for behavioral targeted advertising by turning off “Functional and Performance” and “Advertising” cookies in the cookie settings that can be accessed from the Your Privacy Choices link in the footer of the Visible Offers site, or by managing your settings through the cookie banner that displays on your first visit to the site. If you opt out of Functional and Performance and Advertising cookies, only web tech that is required for the site to function will operate during your visit. Your opt out will apply on the browser and device you used when you opted out. If you visit the site from a different device or browser, or clear your cookies from your browser history, you will need to opt out again. The Visible Offers site also honor browser-based [Global Privacy Control](https://globalprivacycontrol.org/) (GPC) signals that you may set in your browser, as an opt out when you visit the Offers site. 

We require you to verify your identity using the processes described in the portal before we fulfill your request.

We will endeavor to respond to your requests within 45 days, but it may take up to 90 days. If we need more than 45 days, we will contact you to let you know that we need additional time.

Are you a Visible Merch Store customer? Please visit the [Visible Merch Store Privacy Policy](https://www.visiblemerch.com/visible/privacy-policy) for information about how to exercise your rights.

Are you a Visible Communities user?  Please visit the [Visible Community Privacy Policy](https://community.visible.com/t5/Get-Started/Privacy-Policy/ba-p/2) for information about how to exercise your rights.

**VIRGINIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

The Virginia Consumer Data Protection Act gives residents certain rights as it relates to personal information. These rights include the right to access and delete certain information we collect about you; to request that we correct information that you believe is inaccurate; to opt out of having personal information about you sold, used for targeted advertising to you, or used to build a profile about you to make legally or similar significant decisions about you; and to appeal the denial of a request to exercise one of these privacy rights.

**Personal information we collect and how we use it.**

This privacy policy details our collection and use practices. We collect personal information when you interact with us and use our products and services, such as when you place an order or have questions about your account or service; contact us on social media; seek technical support; enter a Visible-sponsored or affiliated contest, sweepstakes, or promotion; or register to receive news or updates. We also collect information from certain third-party sources and from the devices you use.  Depending on what products and services you use and how you interact with us, we may collect these categories of personal information:

* Contact and device information (including name, billing and email address, mobile device identifiers, IP address and account credentials); information about the products and services you purchase; information about your browsing, search and other activity on our sites and app as well as your interactions with our sites, app and advertisements.
    
* Demographic and interest information that you provide or that we obtain from third parties.
    
* Geolocation information from our app when you permit it; information about how you use our products and services; and chat transcripts when you engage with us.
    
* Secure Account Information including account log-in, financial account, debit card, or credit card number in combination with any required security or access code, password, or credentials allowing access to an account 
    
* And other information that may identify, relate to, describe, or is capable of being associated with you. 

Some of the information that we collect is considered sensitive personal information under Virginia law. The law defines sensitive personal information as personal data revealing racial or ethnic origin, religious beliefs, mental or physical health diagnosis, sexual orientation, or citizenship or immigration status; processing genetic or biometric data for the purpose of uniquely identifying you; personal data collected from a known child; and precise geolocation data.

We use this information for business and commercial purposes which include: providing you products and services, operating our businesses, and engaging in economic activities such as communicating with you and providing customer service; personalizing your experiences; improving our services; providing marketing and advertising; debugging; auditing our processes and services; short-term transient uses; research; and security, fraud, and legal compliance. 

Service providers we use to do work on our behalf may use information for the same purposes. We share information with service providers (also known as processors) as necessary for them to perform work for us. They are required to protect the information they receive from us or collect on our behalf and use it only for the specific purposes we allow. We may also disclose information for legal compliance, fraud detection, with your consent and as further described in other sections of this policy.

**You have the right to access and correct information.**

You can access specific pieces and categories of personal information we collected by accessing our [Data and Privacy Portal](https://www.visible.com/legal/data-and-privacy-portal) or via the email address provided below. To the extent technically feasible, we will provide this information to you in a portable and readily usable format. You can use this same contact information to request that we correct personal information we have about you that you believe may be inaccurate.    

**You have the right to delete information.** 

You have the right to request that Visible delete personal information we have about you unless we need it for specific reasons. These reasons include complying with laws, rules, regulations, investigative subpoena or summons by governmental authorities; defending against legal claims; providing and maintaining the products and services you use and preventing security incidents. All the personal information we retain today  is only used for these purposes. We retain information only as long as necessary for these purposes and then securely delete it.  

**You have the right to tell us not to sell personal information or use it for profiling in furtherance of decisions that produce legal or similarly significant effect.**

Virginia law defines “sale” to mean the exchange of personal data for monetary consideration. We do not sell information as it is defined under Virginia law. We also do not use personal information to profile you to further decisions that have legal or similar significant effects.  

**You have the right to opt-out of targeted advertising.**

Virginia law describes “targeted advertising” as using information from your activities over time and across non-affiliated websites or apps to predict your preferences or interests and target our advertising to you.   

Our activities that fall under the definition of “targeted advertising” under the Virginia law are:

* using third-party advertising companies’ cookies, pixels, tags, and other web technologies on our site to collect  information about your activity on our site during your visit  which can be used and combined with other information about you from your activity and behavior across unaffiliated websites and apps to tailor the ads you see from us and others;
    
* sharing consumer information with third-party advertising and social media companies to help them better target our advertising on their websites and applications and to help find other potential customers using interest segments and audiences they create from your activities across non-affiliated websites and apps; and
    
* using consumer information we obtain from third-parties to better customize our advertising, when that information is derived from your activities across non-affiliated sites and apps.

Your can opt out of targeted advertising by accessing [Your Privacy Choices](https://www.visible.com/legal/privacy-choices) .

**Use of sensitive personal information.**

Virginia law prohibits us from using sensitive personal information without your consent, except for specific purposes specified in the law, including: complying with laws, rules, regulations, investigative subpoena or summons by governmental authorities; defending against legal claims; providing and maintaining the products and services you use; preventing and responding to security and other significant incidents; and taking immediate steps to protect an interest that is essential for the life or physical safety of you or another natural person. The law also allows for short-term transient purposes such as displaying relevant information to you based on your activity during a single interaction.   

We do not use sensitive personal information without your express consent or as authorized under the law. 

**You have the right to appeal.**

You can appeal a denial of your request to exercise any of the privacy rights provided by Virginia law. If we deny your request, we will notify you. You may submit an appeal using a link in the notice we provide.  You also may submit an appeal by emailing us at [privacy@visible.com](mailto:privacy@visible.com) . Please use the subject line "APPEAL" and provide your name, contact information including phone number, a description of the decision you are appealing, and the reason for your appeal.  

**We do not discriminate against you.**

We do not discriminate against you if you exercise any rights described in this section, by denying you goods or services, charging different prices or rates for goods or services or providing you a different level or quality of goods and services.  

**Where to exercise your rights.**

You can exercise your right to access, delete, or correct data by:

* Visiting the Visible [Data and Privacy Portal](https://www.visible.com/legal/data-and-privacy-portal)
    
* Sending an email to [privacy@visible.com](mailto:privacy@visible.com) 

You can exercise your right to opt-out of targeted advertising by visiting our [Your Privacy Choices](https://www.visible.com/legal/privacy-choices)  page. 

If you visit or use one of our other sites you must separately opt out using these sites’ “Your Privacy Choices” webpages at [Visible Community Your Privacy Choices](http://community.visible.com/t5/custom/page/page-id/yourprivacychoices) or in the footer on the [Visible Merch website](https://www.visiblemerch.com/).

If you visit Visible Offers, you will have to separately opt out. We use third-party advertising companies that collect information about your visit to the Visible Offers site using cookies and other web technologies to better tailor advertising to you for us and others. You can opt out of the sale and use and sharing of your activity for behavioral targeted advertising by turning off “Functional and Performance” and “Advertising” cookies in the cookie settings that can be accessed from the Your Privacy Choices link in the footer of the Visible Offers site, or by managing your settings through the cookie banner that displays on your first visit to the site. If you opt out of Functional and Performance and Advertising cookies, only web tech that is required for the site to function will operate during your visit. Your opt out will apply on the browser and device you used when you opted out. If you visit the site from a different device or browser, or clear your cookies from your browser history, you will need to opt out again. The Visible Offers site also honors browser-based [Global Privacy Control](https://globalprivacycontrol.org/) (GPC) signals that you may set in your browser, as an opt out when you visit the Offers site. 

We require you to verify your identity using the processes described in the portal before we fulfill your request.

We will endeavor to respond to your requests within 45 days, but it may take up to 90 days. If we need more than 45 days, we will contact you to let you know that we need additional time.

Are you a Visible Merch Store customer? Please visit the [Visible Merch Store Privacy Policy](https://www.visiblemerch.com/visible/privacy-policy) for information about how to exercise your rights.

Are you a Visible Communities user?  Please visit the [Visible Community Privacy Policy](https://community.visible.com/t5/Get-Started/Privacy-Policy/ba-p/2) for information about how to exercise your rights.

**VIII. Changes to the Privacy Policy**

We may make changes to this privacy policy, so please check back periodically. You will be able to see that we made changes by checking the effective date above.  If we decide to use or disclose information that identifies you personally in a way that is materially different from what we stated in our privacy policy at the time we collected that information from you, we will give you a choice about the new use or disclosure by appropriate means, which may include an opportunity to opt-out.

**IX. Still Have Questions?**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our practices, please contact us at [privacy@visible.com](mailto:privacy@visible.com) .

### Data and Privacy Portal

Learn more about how to view and manage your data in the Your Account section of our Help page. Learn more about how to view and manage data collected by other Visible services can be found in the  [Visible Community Privacy Policy](https://community.visible.com/t5/Get-Started/Privacy-Policy/ba-p/2) and the [Visible Merch Store Privacy Policy](https://www.visiblemerch.com/visible/privacy-policy).

To appeal a privacy rights decision, you can email us at [privacy@visible.com](mailto:privacy@visible.com). Use the word "APPEAL" in your subject line and provide a description of the decision you are appealing, including a request ID if you have one. You may also use this email for any privacy rights requests you wish to submit.

### **Here are the most recent changes to our Privacy Policy.**

We review and update our Privacy Policy to reflect the changes that come with the development of new products, services, technologies and uses of information. In addition, we occasionally make organizational, stylistic and grammatical changes to make our policy easier to read. Below you’ll find an overview of the changes that have been made in the past six months.

**December 2023:**  
We made changes to clarify and provide additional details about our collection, use and sharing practices. We made changes to the state laws section of our privacy policy. Specifically, we added new information about the privacy rights provided by the Utah privacy law and updated information we have in the California, Colorado, Connecticut and Virginia sections to make them more uniform.

**July 2023:**

We made changes to clarify and provide additional details about our collection, use and sharing practices. We made changes to the state laws section of our privacy policy. Specifically, we added new information about the privacy rights provided by the Colorado and Connecticut privacy laws and updated information we have in the California and Virginia sections to make them more uniform.

### Cookies, Pixels, Tags, Web Beacons, and Scripts, or Similar Technologies

Cookies, beacons, tags, scripts and similar technologies are tools that websites can use for a variety of purposes. Examples of the ways we use these tools include improving website and app security, authenticating you, detecting and deterring fraud, improving site performance, improving site navigation and fixing bugs, recognizing you as a registered user and remembering your settings and preferences, site analytics and providing more personalized content.  Third parties that operate on our site use the data they collect for the same purposes or may use the information to help determine what parts of our sites or emails are more interesting to you to better provide Verizon advertising on other sites and apps. These providers may also combine information they obtain from our site with information they collect from other sites to better target Verizon and other advertisements to you. 

**Types of Website Tools**

Cookies.  A cookie is a small string of data that is written on your computer browser when you visit a website. Cookies enable the websites themselves as well as third parties present on the website to recognize and maintain information about your visit to the site. A cookie’s data string usually includes a unique user ID that the website or cookie provider can use to customize your experience and reach you with relevant advertising on other sites, apps and devices. Verizon uses cookies on our sites to help us  provide you with a more relevant experience on our site and more relevant Verizon ads in other places.  Our sites may use different kinds of cookies, including HTTP cookies (also known as browser cookies) and Local Shared Objects such as Flash cookies that are built for use with the Adobe® Flash® Player.

**Web beacons and pixels.**  We deploy our own and third-party web beacons and pixels on our sites and in our emails to better understand what content users access. Web beacons and pixels are usually clear .gif files, electronic images that allow the collection of information about your interactions on our sites.  Web beacons and pixels may be used to understand website traffic patterns and the number of visitors to different pages of our website, and to measure the effectiveness of advertisements or email advertising messages.

**Website data scripts and tags.**  We may embed  website scripts or tags (small snippets of code) to record and send data about  content that a user accesses on the site.  Website scripts and tags may be used to optimize and measure marketing campaigns and segment user profiles.

**Social networks and other third-party plug-ins and widgets.**

Verizon sites also include social network or other third-party plug-ins and widgets that may provide information back to their associated social networks or third-parties about the Verizon page you visit, even if you do not click on or otherwise interact with the plug-in or widget and regardless of whether you have an account or other relationship with these social networks and third-parties. If you use social network tools or visit social networking sites, you should read their privacy disclosures and learn about your choices. 

**Your Choices**

You can limit the sharing of website information when the use is for certain types of targeted advertising. Visit [Your Privacy Choices](https://www.visible.com/legal/privacy-choices)  [to learn about how you can opt out.](https://www.verizon.com/privacy/your-privacy-choices) This page also describes how we honor [Global Privacy Control](https://globalprivacycontrol.org/) signals you may set on your browser. We do not respond to Do Not Track signals. 

The Digital Advertising Alliance provides you the ability to prevent the use of third party cookies or advertising identifiers to provide interest-based advertising to you across the sites, apps and devices you use. You can opt out of this type of interest-based advertising at the [DAA opt out page](http://optout.aboutads.info/). You can opt out for mobile apps on your mobile device.  Apple devices allow apps to include interest-based advertising only if you opt in using the app’s pop-up notice. You can change your choice using Apple device settings. On Android devices, you can opt out using your device setting to “Opt out of Ads Personalization”.

You can also manage cookies  using features and functions available on most Internet browsers that allow you to delete or disable cookies and even choose what types of cookies may be placed on your device. More information about cookie controls for specific browsers can be found here:

Please be aware that disabling cookies may prevent you from using specific features on our sites and other sites, such as ordering products or services and maintaining an online account. 

Cookies associated with your Flash Player may be removed by managing your settings with Adobe. [Learn more about flash cookies including how to delete or prevent placement of flash cookies](https://www.adobe.com/privacy/policies/flash-player.html).

Please note that some of the controls described above are device or browser-based. You will need to record your choices on each device or browser where you want them to be in place. In addition, your opt-outs may be stored via cookies. If you clear your cookies, please check to make sure your opt-outs are in place. 

Updated: December, 2023

Main region ended

Footer region started

Follow Visible:

Subscribe to stay in the loop.

 Submit Email address

That is not a valid email format. Please try again.

Apps

Plans

Services

Shop

Company

* * *

Follow Visible:

Subscribe to stay in the loop.

 Submit Email address

That is not a valid email format. Please try again..

* * *

Apps

Plans

Apps

Plans

Services

Shop

Company

* * *

 [](https://www.visible.com/)© 2023 Visible. All rights reserved.

10000 Park Meadows Drive Suite 200, Lone Tree, CO 80124

 [](https://www.visible.com/)© 2023 Visible. All rights reserved. 10000 Park Meadows Drive Suite 200, Lone Tree, CO 80124

 [](https://www.visible.com/)© 2023 Visible. All rights reserved.

10000 Park Meadows Drive Suite 200, Lone Tree, CO 80124

Footer region ended
